{
    "subject": "resource/Wells_Fargo",
    "predicate": "property/hasPhotoCollection",
    "object": "http://wifo5-03.informatik.uni-mannheim.de/flickrwrappr/photos/Wells_Fargo",
    "human_readable": "Wells Fargo has a photo collection.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9830325245857239,
            "question": "Does Wells Fargo possess a photo collection?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9822829365730286,
            "question": "Is there a photo collection associated with Wells Fargo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8695052862167358,
            "question": "What does Wells Fargo have a collection of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8484904766082764,
            "question": "What kind of collection does Wells Fargo have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7365636229515076,
            "question": "Wells Fargo owns what kind of collection?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7263762354850769,
            "question": "What kind of things are included in Wells Fargo's collection?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7043222784996033,
            "question": "What is the subject of Wells Fargo's collection?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6986547112464905,
            "question": "What type of items are in Wells Fargo's collection?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6933750510215759,
            "question": "Does Wells Fargo curate a collection?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6157493591308594,
            "question": "What type of material is held in Wells Fargo's collection?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Wells Fargo has a photo collection.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4995_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Wells Fargo curate a collection?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4995_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of items are in Wells Fargo's collection?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4995_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the subject of Wells Fargo's collection?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4995_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4995_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4995_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4995_138.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4995_152.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4995_154.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4995_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4995_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4995_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4995_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4995_50.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can conclude that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention \"Wells Fargo reserves the right to accept or reject any artwork\" (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4995/re-ranker-msmarco/120.txt) and \"Personalize your Wells Fargo Card with images that reflect what\u2019s important to you.\" (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4995/re-ranker-msmarco/35.txt), which implies that Wells Fargo has a collection of images or photos."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention specific instances related to Wells Fargo and photos, such as the Wiltsee Collection of almost 1,400 covers representing California towns and express companies, including Wells Fargo. This supports the statement that Wells Fargo has a photo collection."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}